http://www.bishopsport.co.uk/privacy-policy.html

Bishop Group of Companies Privacy PolicyBishop Sports & Leisure Ltd is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the security of any personal information received from you. We strictly adhere to the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in the UK. The purpose of this statement is to explain to you what personal information we collect, the purpose for collecting it and how we may use it. We process personal information to enable us to carry out the principal activities of the Group, namely the manufacture, importation and sale (both home and export) of sports, educational and recreational goods and equipment. We also process personal information to manage properties, promote and advertise our services, maintain our accounts and records, undertake market research and support and manage our employees. We process personal information about employees, customers, complainants, enquirers, advisers and consultants, suppliers and service providers, offenders and suspected offenders and individuals captured by CCTV. We process information relevant to the above reasons/purposes which may include personal details, financial details, visual images, goods and services for all and relative to employee’s only, family details, lifestyle and social circumstances, education and employment details and personal appearance and behaviour. We also process sensitive classes of information with regards to employees which may include physical or mental health details, offences and alleged offences and criminal proceedings, outcomes and sentences. We collect this information from you through written correspondence, telephone conversations and the use of our website. When you order, we need to know your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and payment details. This allows us to process and fulfil your order. You have the option to withhold personal information that is not required for the order process. We use your personal information to notify you of your purchase and to send you updates of our products and services. We will only contact you with your consent. We do not sell or rent your personal information with any third party for commercial reasons, beyond the essential requirement for credit/debit card validation during purchase. Where necessary or required we share information with family, associates and representatives of the person whose personal data we are processing, business associates and professional advisors, other companies within the same Group, service providers and suppliers, financial organisations, trade unions and associations, police and security forces, current, past and prospective employers, credit reference agencies and central government. We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access in accordance with the GDPR. In order to maintain the accuracy of our database, you can check, update or remove your personal details by e-mailing data@bishopgroup.co.uk. Any requests will be processed within 30days at no charge unless they are manifestly unfounded or excessive in which case we reserve the right to refuse or charge for the request. We use a technology called "cookies" as part of a normal business procedure to track patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. A cookie is an element of data that our website sends to your browser which is then stored on your system. You can set your browser to prevent this happening. Any information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you change your browser settings. In order to process credit/debit card transactions, the bank or card processing agency may require to verify your personal details for authorisation outside the EEA (European Economic Area). Your information will not be transferred outside the EEA for any other purpose. If you have any questions about privacy please contact us at data@bishopgroup.co.uk.Social news feeds
Bishop Sports & Leisure
Tweets by BishopSport
Customer ServiceSite Go Top All Products
Site Map Sports Categories Vacancies [1]Bishops Contact Us About Us Ordering Terms & Conditions Privacy Policy TradeMore A Guide Making a Difference Downloads eCatalogue BSL Image LibrarySocial© 2020 Bishop Sports & Leisure Ltd.
Sign Up For Our Newsletter & SAVE Special Offers, whilst stocks last! HomeSports/CategoriesYouth Sport TrustActive Early YearsActive Play & ExerciseActive Play - InclusiveArcheryAthleticsBadmintonBasketballBocciaBowlsBoxingChanging Room & Cloakroom FunitureCheerleadingCoaching & Training ResourcesCones & MarkersCricketCurlingDance, Movement & Rhythmic GymnasticsDodgeballExercise, Health & FitnessFirst AidFootballGames - Indoor & OutdoorGames KitGoal Post SafetyGoalballGolf & Mini GolfGym, Sports Mats & TrolleysGymnasticsHandballHarrod UKHockeyInclusive SportsLacrosseLine MarkingNetballOrienteeringPlayground EquipmentPublicationsRoundersRugbyScoreboards & Sports TimingSnooker & PoolSoftball, Baseball & American FootballSquash & RacketballStoolballStorage EquipmentSwimming & Water SafetyTable TennisTchoukballTennisTrampolines & TrampettesVolleyballContact UsAbout UsHow to orderDownloadsMaking a differenceeCatalogue  View Basket | Wish List | New Account | Sign In
